Katrina C. Alegre / Web Developer

Phone: +639179711327 | Email: katrina.c.alegre@gmail.com

Address: 85 Intan St. Bagong Barrio Caloocan City

Portfolio: https://katrinaalegre.github.io/katrina-alegre/



OBJECTIVE

I would like to contribute to your organization as a Web Developer, levering my ability to develop creative websites, develop E - Commerce web applications using readily available frameworks. With my passion for learning, I will be able to take part in empowering your team with my newly found coding expertise.

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- · Basic knowledge in Javascript, JQuery, PHP
- · Basic knowledge in MySQL
- · Adobe Illustrator
- Basic Photoshop
- · Laravel Framework

UI/UX

- · Terminal and Command Line Interface
- Version Control GIT/ GITHUB
- Software Development Life Cycle
- · Wireframing and Prototyping
- · Debugging

PROJECT EXPERINCE

TUITT CODING BOOTCAMP

Capstone 3 - November 2018 - December 2018

- A Blog Site using Laravel Framework
- Users can Register, Login and Comment on a Blog using Disgus.
- Admin can Create, Retrieve, Update and Delete a Blog
- Environment: Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap Javascript, JQery and Laravel

Capstone 1 - September 2018 - October 2018

- · A Static Website
- · Website using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap

Capstone 2 - October 2018 - November 2018

- A Blog Site using Laravel Framework
- Users can Register, Login and Comment on a Blog using Disqus.
- Admin can Create, Retrieve, Update and Delete a Blog
- Environment: Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap Javascript, JQery and Laravel

WORKING EXPERIENCE

MEDICAL CLAIMS ANALYST

Imagenet Philippines | May 2015 - July 2018

- Verifies, audits medical claims to ensure the accuracy of company reinbursement payments.
- Check for conflicts, errors or inconsistencies to the Health Insurance policies.

DATA ANALYST

Accenture Inc. | June 2009 - December 2012

- Verifying and updating information on submitted claims, reviewing the policy to determine which charges are eligible for reimbursement.
- Provides immediate resolution regarding issues in claims processing using different systems.

EDUCATION

480 HOURS OF INTENSIVE WEB DEVELOPMENT COURSE

TUITT Coding Bootcamp | Sept 2018 - Dec 2018

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Manila Central University - June 2004 - March 2008